Draw it properly.
ちゃんと描いてて
You're fine, Jinko.
元気でしょ、ジンコ
Too energetic.
元気すぎる
Are you too energetic?
元気すぎる?
You're catching it properly, Jinko.
ちゃんと捕まえてる、ジンコ
The person who passed away in an instant,
さっき一瞬でお亡くなりしてくれた人は、
I have to give something back.
お返ししなきゃいけない
Give it back.
返してあげて
It's getting hot.
暑くなってきた
We'll take our clothes off.
俺ら脱いじゃうね
I'll take it off now.
脱いじゃいましまーす
Is it hot?
暑いか
It's hot, already.
暑くて、もう
Sura-chan was still wearing her clothes.
ス ラちゃんは、着たままで
Sura-chan, it's okay to leave this on.
スラちゃん、これ着たままからはいいから
Ah, what a shame.
ああ、惜しい
Let me continue.
俺の続きしてあげて
Yeah.
うん
Sura-chan, right?
スラちゃんさ、ね
Isn't today a fantan shower festival?
今日ってさ、ファンタンシャワー祭じゃない?
A while ago and up until now, you've been making multiple stories into one, haven't you?
さっきも今までも、複数でさ、一編にしてたじゃない?
I'm begging you, but hey, everyone is like that.
お願いなんだけど、 ちょっと、みんなそうですよね
I wanted to have a one-on-one session with Sura-chan.
1対1で、ちょっと、スラちゃんとしたいなって
I see.
なるほど
copper?
どう?
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
So, uh, what are we going to do? That's all.
じゃあ、あの、何するんか、あれだけ
In order, then.
順番にね、じゃあ
Ah, okay, okay, in order.
あ、いいです、いいですよ、順番で
Do you want to go with Jangi?
ジャンギで行きますか、順番
It's Jangi.
ジャンギね
Well then, let's go in order and jump.
じゃ、順番、ジャンギで行きましょう
Are men okay too?
男もいい?
No, I lost.
いやー、負けた
I won.
勝っちゃいました
Hey, I won.
ちょっと、勝っちゃった
I won.
勝っちゃった
Is it the one who won?
勝った人かな?
I won
勝 っちゃ
It was.
った
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I won't cut it.
切らないよ
I want this time to last.
この時間が続いてほしい
10 minutes is a short time, isn't it?
10分とかも短いでしょ
Yeah.
うん
Take a moment and look behind you.
ちょっと、後ろを反対に見てほら
behind?
後ろ?
Yeah.
うん
It's okay to take it slow.
ゆっくりでいいよ
Can you raise your knees?
膝を上げられる?
Yeah.
うん
It looked like an asshole.
お尻の穴のままに見えたよ
Glue it more firmly to the bottom to make it stick.
下にもっとベタっとくっついてくっつけるの
That's right, it's stuck together low and sticky.
そうそう、低くベタっとくっついてあって
Oh yeah, so move it slowly and see.
そうそう、それでゆっくり動かしてほら
move?
動かす?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Yeah, that's right.
うん、そう
Because your butt is beautiful.
お尻がきれいだからさ
Yeah.
うん
what up?
どうした?
Can you see if someone enters?
人が入っても見える?
Yeah.
うん
yeah?
ん?
Can't you see?
見えないの?
Yeah.
うん
It's in there, right?
入ってるでしょ?
what happened?
どうしたの?
My stomach disappeared.
お腹消えちゃった
Should you go by yourself?
あなた、自分で行こうかな?
Yeah.
うん
My stomach disappeared.
お 腹消えちゃった
It's a little hot, isn't it?
ちょっと暑いでしょ?
You can sleep.
寝 ていいよ
Let's just remove the top.
上だけ抜こう
You'll lose air.
空気抜けちゃうね
Just remove the top.
上だけ抜いちゃいな
Yes, I slept.
はい、寝ました
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Saba-chan, just like before.
さばちゃん、さっきのさ
Saba-chan feels good.
さばちゃん、気持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Saba-chan, can I take it out?
さ ば ちゃん、出してもいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Look it's gone.
抜けたってごらん
Look with both hands.
両手でごらん
Spread your legs for yourself.
足広げてごらん、自分で
It's okay to do it hard.
激しくやっていいよ
kiss me.
キスして
Saba-chan, let's go.
さばちゃん、行きそう
I'll put it out.
出すよ
Do you understand?
わかる?
Let's go out, Saba-chan.
出てみよう、さばちゃん